Myth number 1, you are supposed to use your dog's name before you give him every command to get his attention.
Wrong.
Use your dog's name for common heel.
Those are the action commands.
The stationary commands are sit down and stay.
You never want to use your dog's name for those commands.
First thing people do when they bring their puppy or dog home is that they name them.
They'll say Lucky.
The dog will start moving towards him.
Eventually they can add Lucky come, the dog starts moving over.
If your dog is sitting there and you say Lucky down, he may towards you and then you may get mad at him.
Now he is really confused or Lucky stay.
So all that does is cause confusion.
Sit down and stay.
Those are the stationary commands.
Never use the dog's name for those.